const STORE = [{
    question: 'Where is Fixer Upper filmed?',
    answers: [
      'Houston, TX',
      'Dallas, TX',
      'Austin, TX',
      'Waco, TX'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Waco, TX',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/icBTO4G',
    alt: 'Chip and Joanna Picture'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many kids do Chip and Joanna have?',
    answers: [
      '2',
      '3',
      '4, with another on the way',
      '5'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '4, with another on the way',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/beGqFyV',
    alt: 'Chip and Joanna with family'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where was Joanna born?',
    answers: [
      'Kansas',
      'Kentucky',
      'Arkansas',
      'Texas'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Kansas',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/w9Q8ZKK',
    alt: 'A single golden ear of wheat waving in the wind against a bright sky'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where was Chip born?',
    answers: [
      'Oklahoma',
      'Missouri',
      'New Mexico',
      'Mississippi'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'New Mexico',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/axUxgjZ',
    alt: 'Cacti'
  },
  {
    question: 'What university did Chip and Joanna both attend?',
    answers: [
      'Texas A&M',
      'Baylor',
      'UT Austin',
      'Texas State University'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Baylor',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/37BXuAu',
    alt: 'Baylor University main building'
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of Chip and Joanna's first store?",
    answers: [
      'Magnolia',
      'Orchid',
      'Tulip',
      'Hydrangea'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Magnolia',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/XEsYQVo',
    alt: 'Magnolia store'
  },
  {
    question: 'When did Chip flip his first house?',
    answers: [
      'During high school',
      'During college',
      'In his mid-twenties',
      'On the first season of Fixer Upper'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'During college',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/2PLyjmy',
    alt: 'Old house that needs to be fixed up'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Joanna\'s favorite way to decorate walls?',
    answers: [
      'Shiplap',
      'Lots of wood frames',
      'Vintage American flags',
      'Cedar paneling'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Shiplap',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/bB0r3sb',
    alt: 'Little sitting area with white shiplap on walls'
  },
  {
    question: 'How did they get their own show?',
    answers: [
      'They just applied on HGTV\'s website - duh!',
      'HGTV approached them after they saw pictures of a recent flip house Chip and Joanna did',
      'They had a friend working at HGTV who referred them',
      'Joanna\'s mom called HGTV and told them about Chip and Joanna'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'HGTV approached them after they saw pictures of a recent flip house Chip and Joanna did',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/tfyV0rI',
    alt: 'Chip and Joanna posing for Fixer Upper'
  },
  {
    question: 'What style do they use most when decorating the houses?',
    answers: [
      'Modern',
      'Rustic',
      'French Country',
      'Mid-century'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'French Country',
    icon: 'https://imgur.com/a/dhzhCjl',
    alt: 'French country style house from Fixer Upper'
  }
];